Hey, slow down, Mike, okay? You're making me sick.
麥克 慢一點 你害我想吐
I would slow down if you hadn't already made us late.
你沒害我們遲到我就會慢一點
We're... We're not late, okay? You're just anxious.
我們沒遲到 你只是著急
No, I'm anxious 'cause you made us late.
你害我們遲到我才會著急
I'm not doin' this with you in the next phase of our lives.
我以後不會再忍受你了
You're gon' respect my time.
你要尊重我的時間
My stomach. My stomach.
我肚子不舒服
Hey, Mike, look, pull over at that store right there.
麥克 在那家店靠邊停車
I need a ginger ale.
我需要薑汁汽水
Look, we don't have no time to get no ginger ale, man.
沒時間買汽水啦
Come on, Mike, I'm sick.
拜託 麥克 我不舒服
You're freaking me out, okay?
你把我嚇壞了
I feel like I'm gonna throw... throw up.
我就快要吐了
I dare you, Marcus.
你敢給我吐試試看
You got 90 seconds, all right?
你只有90秒
Ginger ale and nothing else.
只准買汽水 其他不行
I am a grown-ass man, okay?
我是個成年人 好嗎?
Just be nice.
口氣好一點
Oh. Okay. 85 seconds.
好喔 85秒
Are those dogs fresh?
那些熱狗新鮮嗎?
I put 'em on yesterday.
昨天放進去的
Well, give me one and put some relish and some mustard on that motherfucker.
給我來一根 芥末醬和酸黃瓜塗好放滿
Hook it up. Come on, hurry up.
手腳快點 快
No, that one right there. Yeah. Yeah, that right there. Hurry up.
那一根 對 快點
Gotta go, gotta go.
我得閃了
Don't be takin' your time.
別給我慢慢來
Yeah, my man.
好耶 老兄
Hey, open the register.
打開收銀機
No, no, no. Now!
不不不 馬上!
Sir, today is not the day.
刺青哥 今天別惹我
Shut the fuck up!
給我閉嘴!
Look, if I'm not in that car in 15 seconds,
聽好 我15秒內再不上車
there's a very surly man that's comin' in here and we both are fucked.
就會有個暴怒男衝進來教訓我們
Marcus. Hey, don't fuckin' move.
馬可斯 乖乖別動
The fuck over there!
給我站住!
'Ey, Mike, I told this guy I had to go.
麥克 我跟他說我得閃了
Is that Skittles on the counter, Marcus?
櫃台上是彩虹糖嗎?
Well, he was takin' a long time with the ginger ale.
他找很久才找到薑汁汽水
That is incorrect. He grabbed that ginger ale the second he came in here.
才不是 他一進門就拿了汽水
A hot dog, Marcus?
你在吃熱狗 馬可斯?
You're not supposed to be eatin' that shit.
你不該吃那種垃圾食物
This is not mine, Mike. Yes, it is.
不是我的 麥克 是你的
Mind your business with your tattletaling ass.
你這大嘴巴別多管閒事
Everybody shut the fuck up!
都給我閉嘴!
Sir, I'm gonna need you to lower your weapon.
先生 我得請你放下武器
Come take my weapon, then, motherfucker.
過來搶啊 混帳東西
Don't antagonise him.
別惹毛他
Marcus, get in the car.
馬可斯 上車
Mike, he has a gun to my head.
他拿槍抵住我的頭耶
Wanna deal with him, you wanna deal with me?
你要聽他的還是聽我的?
Sorry, sir, but I gotta go.
抱歉 但我得閃了
You didn't have to shoot him, Mike.
你不必開槍射他 麥克
Get in the car.
給我上車
Call 911.
打電話報警
Aren't you the police?
你不就是警察嗎?
Other people look at you
其他人看到你
and see the tailored suits, the cars, the watches.
只看到高級西裝、超跑和名錶
I met you without any of that.
當我遇到你 你一無所有
Stripped, basically naked...
全身幾乎被剝光
which is 90% of why I'm marrying you.
那是我嫁給你的九成原因
I met you at your lowest.
我在你的低潮遇見你
You'd been shot.
你受到槍傷
But there was a fire in you that was...
但你心中的那股熊熊烈火
...extraordinary.
讓你發光發熱
And I vow to spend the rest of my life fanning that flame.
我發誓用盡一生為你加油打氣
I now pronounce you...
我現在宣布你們
husband and wife.
正式成為夫妻
You may kiss the bride.
你可以親吻新娘
Yes!
讚啦!
I love it.
超浪漫的
You know, it kinda makes sense that he married his therapist after he got shot.
他受傷後娶了治療師其實很合理
I love that for him. Mental health is super important.
我為他高興 心理健康很重要
Well, it was his physical therapist.
她是物理治療師
Congratulations, Michael. Rita. Thank you, thank you.
恭喜了 麥克 莉塔 謝謝妳
Mr Mayor.
市長先生
Oh, not yet. Don't jinx it. I'm still just a lowly US Attorney.
還不是 話別說太早 我只是檢察官
I've been watching what you're doin'.
我一直在關注你
You got my vote. Thank you.
我會投你一票 謝謝
Congratulations to you.
我也要恭喜你們
I mean, the definition of a power couple right there.
你們是標準的超強情侶檔
I'll grab you a drink. Okay.
我替妳拿杯酒 好
Can I get you anything? No, I'm good, thank you.
你喝什麼?不了 謝謝
And all this time, I thought you were a terminal bachelor.
我一直以為你永遠都會單身
I... I... I even surprised myself with this one.
這次連我自己都沒想到
Yeah, I guess you just hadn't met the right one.
我猜之前你還沒遇到天命真女
I had some growing up to do.
我得學會長大
You were 50.
那時候你都50歲了
Okay.
好吧
I'm gonna pre-apologise for whatever he says.
我要先為他要講的話道歉
Mike.
麥克
No, you know how it is. Don't... Marcus!
馬可斯 你應該很瞭
Marcus. Come... Let me get it out!
馬可斯 讓我一吐為快
Come on, man.
夠了 兄弟
Everything you have been through, man. Okay.
我們一起經歷這麼多 好啦
The witch. The Bruja.
那個女巫婆
The prostitute.
那個妓女
My sister. 'Member? You coulda told me about my sister, Mike.
我老妹 記得嗎?你們交往不該瞞著我
You coulda told me that.
你應該跟我說
I would've embraced you, if that's who she was feeling.
如果她愛你 我也會接受
I love you, Mike. No doubt.
我愛你 麥克 毫無疑問
You know, Cap would've loved to have been here to see this.
隊長肯定會想看到這一切
But you know what?
但你們知道嗎?
We got his daughter, Judy, and his granddaughter, Callie.
他女兒茱蒂和外孫女卡莉都來了
She wants to say something.
她想說幾句話
My grandad loved you guys.
我外公很愛你們
And if he were here, he would have told you not to F this up.
他如果還在 就會叫你別搞砸
That's what he would've said.
他會這麼說啊
Yeah, he woulda said "Don't fuck it up."
他會說“別他媽的搞砸”
Exactly.
一點都沒錯
Oh, excuse me.
等我一下下
Mike, you been my partner a long time.
麥克 我們搭檔了很久
Yes, sir.
沒錯
Now he's gonna be your partner, Christine.
現在他是妳的搭檔 克莉絲汀
To Mike and Christine Lowrey.
敬麥克和克莉絲汀勞里
For life! For life!
一生一世! 一生一世!
Go Marcus! Go Marcus! Go Marcus! Go Marcus!
跳啊 馬可斯!
Oh, shit.
噢慘了
What happened? What happened?
發生什麼事?
Marcus. Marcus!
馬可斯!
What's the address?
告訴我地址
Let me in, let me in, let me in. Back up.
讓我來 退後
This is Captain Rita Secada. I have an officer in cardiac arrest.
這是莉塔塞卡達隊長 有位警探心跳停止
Come on, man.
快醒醒
It's not your time.
你的時辰未到
Marcus!
馬可斯!
Marc-Marc--!
馬可!
This guy.
這臭傢伙
Hey, buddy.
嘿 兄弟
What you doing?
你在幹嘛?
I spent my whole life being scared, Mike.
我這輩子都在擔心害怕
I wasted so much time.
浪費了太多時間
Why... Why... Why don't you...Why don't you just step back from the edge a little bit, please.
拜託你往這邊退後一點
What year is it?
今年是哪一年?
It's Tuesday.
今天星期二
Same year your ass was wobbling in.
跟你跳搖臀舞是同一年
Oh, wow. Felt like it was five years.
哇 感覺像是五年前
I was in the basement of the ocean.
我在海底的深處
All my bullshit was gone.
所有的屁事都不見了
Just freedom.
只有自由
And full body love, Mike. Full body love.
全身充滿了愛 滿滿的愛
Okay.
好吧
Why... Why... Why don't you...
你不如
...love your full body back from the ledge, please?
帶著全身的愛往後退 好嗎?
Nothing to be scared of.
沒什麼好怕的
It's not my time, baby. It's not my time.
我的時辰未到 寶貝 時辰未到
Mr Burnett!
班奈特先生!
Hey, I got him.
我搞定了
He's just...
他只是在
I don't know what the fuck he's doing.
我不知道他在搞什麼鬼
But I got it. I got him. We're good. We are good.
但我能搞定 沒事了
We are great! 'Ey...
我們棒呆了!
Miami!
邁阿密!
305 for life!
一生一世!
Kakow!
硬啦!
All right. Just stop. You gon' put somebody's eye out with that thing, man.
夠了喔 你那玩意會傷眼睛
I'm bringing the thunder, Mike. I get it.
我要大發雷霆了 麥克
Bringing the thunder.
大發雷霆
All right. There you go.
好了 這就對了
Oh, man. Bring it in.
好險 來抱一下
Thought I lost you, brother.
我以為會失去你 兄弟
Couldn't lose me if you tried.
你永遠不會失去我
You know your ass is out, right?
你的屁股蛋露出來了
Everybody's ass is out, Mike.
大家都嘛一樣 麥克
Hey.
嘿
There's a storm coming.
一場風暴即將來臨
No. Not that kind of storm.
不 不是那種風暴
You're gonna be tested.
你會受到考驗
Things are gonna get bad,
情況會變得很糟
and you're gonna have to make a really hard choice.
你必須做出艱難抉擇
Just know you're good.
但我會永遠挺你
This is my private time, Mr McGrath.
這是我的私人時間 麥格拉先生
How may I help you?
我能幫你什麼忙?
I need you to move some money. Your money?
我要你轉移一些錢 你的錢?
Your boss's, actually. I need it to be cartel cash.
你老闆的錢 要轉成販毒現金
Just under 20 million.
將近兩千萬美元
Backdated series of transfers beginning 2004, ending January 2020...
更改匯款日期 從2004年到2020年
into...
匯入
...that account.
那個戶頭
In the name of the late Captain Conrad Howard.
已故康瑞德霍華隊長的戶頭
I have people who can handle logistics.
我手下能搞定
I really just need your log-in credentials.
我只需要你的密碼
And why would I give you those?
我憑什麼要給你?
Oh, my God!
天啊!
Come here, darling.
過來 親愛的
Come on.
來啊
Come here.
這就對了
You can't transfer funds from a phone.
你不能用手機匯款
Hey, honey, what's going on?
老公 怎麼了?
Do they know each other?
她們互相認識嗎?
Honey, who's there with you?
老公 那是誰?
All right, all right! Honey--
好啦! 老公?
Here we go.
開始了
They'll kill you for this.
他們會殺了你
They're not even gonna know this happened.
他們根本不會知道
Your girlfriend heard you on the phone with your wife
你的小三聽到你跟老婆講電話
And in a fit of passion, she shot you.
她一時激動開槍射死你
Your bodyguard tried to step in, but he was too late.
你的保鑣試圖阻止 但是太遲了
And realising the horror of her actions...
當她發現自己鑄下大錯
she took her own life.
就舉槍自盡
Honey, what are you doing?
老公 你在幹嘛?
You had a heart attack two weeks ago. Exactly.
你兩週前才心臟病發作 沒錯
They call it a widow-maker for a reason. You need to be in the hospital, baby.
心臟病是寡婦製造者 你得待在醫院
Hey, I tried to told his ass, T.
我跟這死腦筋說過了
Apparently, he's an adult. He was allowed to sign hisself out.
但他是個大人 可以自行出院
Hey, babe. Look, come on. I couldn't take one more second away from you.
寶貝 聽我說 我不能離開妳身邊
All these stents in me got my blood flowing.
這些支架讓我血脈賁張
I'm on D way. All right, now.
我要回家囉 夠了喔
Ey. Ey. Come on, man. That's my phone.
別亂來 那是我的手機
All right, babe. All right. Love you.
好喔 寶貝 我也愛妳
Hey, Mike.
嘿 麥克
I wasn't even gonna tell you this...
我本來不打算告訴你
but this ain't the first time we done this.
但這不是我們的第一次
We ride together all the time, what you mean?
我們常常這樣啊 你在說啥?
No, I'm talking about our souls.
我在說我們的靈魂
You know, we've ridden together, but I saw it all, Mike.
我們一起出勤 但我什麼都懂了
We haven't always been Mike and Marcus, but we've always been us.
不一定是麥克和馬可斯 但永遠是我們
What you talking 'bout?
你在鬼扯什麼?
We're soulmates.
我們是靈魂伴侶
Yup. Yeah.
對吧?是啊
Naw.
才不是
Yeah, I kind of... I saw my soulmate looking a little different than that.
我的靈魂伴侶才不會長這樣
See... See, Mike, you stuck in the physical.
你太注重外表了
Souls don't have dicks.
靈魂沒有老二
I'm pretty sure my soul has a dick, Marcus.
我很確定我的靈魂有大屌
See? That's that shit right there. That's why we're stuck.
你老說這種屁話 所以才沒有長進
You know, I wasn't gonna tell you this shit either,
我本來不打算告訴你
but my soul is more advanced than your soul.
但我靈魂的境界比你的更高
It's not that your soul is stupid.
你的靈魂也不差啦
You know?
你瞭吧?
It's just that you're more like a baby soul. You know?
只是你的靈魂像小寶寶 瞭嗎?
And I'm more like a mother soul.
我的靈魂像一個母親
And I just gotta suckle ya.
我得餵奶給你喝
You know? Put you on that titty.
瞭嗎?讓你吸奶奶
You know?
瞭嗎?
Hey. How long you think your brain went without oxygen?
你的大腦到底缺氧多久?
Daddy! Daddy's home.
爸爸! 爸爸回家了
Baby! Oh, baby, you're back. Where my family? My family.
寶貝 你回來了 我的家人
Hey, baby.
嘿 老婆
Little Marcus!
小馬可斯!
Say hi to Pop-pop. Say hi to Grandad.
跟公公說嗨 跟阿公說嗨
I missed you so-Look at you, woman.
我超想你! 看看妳
No, come on, look at me, baby.
看看我啊 寶貝
We're gonna have to hose them down.
我們得潑他們冷水
All right. All right, we get it. We get it.
夠了喔 我們瞭啦
Put some ice in your drawers or somethin'.
冰鎮一下你的下半身
That's funny.
很搞笑
Are you feeling good, Marcus?
你還好嗎 馬可斯?
I never felt better in my life.
這輩子沒這麼好過
Oh, Marcus, I missed you so much, honey, but you need to get some rest.
老公 我超想你的 但你得好好休息
Oh, no, baby, I need you.
不 寶貝 我需要妳
Just let me get some electrolytes. Okay, baby. Give me a kiss.
先讓我吃點東西 好喔 親一下
So, what's going on with my dad?
我爸是怎麼了?
Well, he was on the roof naked...
他光著屁股跑到屋頂
"Amazing Chickpeas"?
“鷹嘴豆泥醬”?
Oh, and he said I have a stupid baby soul
他還說我的靈魂像小寶寶
with no penis.
沒有小雞雞
Hey, Reggie. Yes, sir.
嘿 雷吉 是 先生
Did you eat my snacks? No, sir.
你吃了我的零食?沒有啊 先生
I was looking forward to my snacks, Reggie.
我很想吃零食耶 雷吉
Honey.
老公
You know what? You need to get a job.
你得找份工作
I'm a US Marine, sir.
我是海軍陸戰隊 先生
Well, then you need to deploy.
那你就得去打仗
You know, we just got back from Yemen.
我才剛從葉門回來
Thank you for your service.
多謝你盡忠職守
You thought I was dead, didn't you? Dead?
你以為我掛了 對吧?掛了?
One thing you don't know, Reggie.
有件事你不知道 雷吉
I got a camera up in here. Yeah.
我在家裡裝了監視器
Theresa!
泰瑞莎!
It's the doctor's orders, Marcus. You're on a strict diet. No salt, no sugar, no fats.
醫生吩咐你要節食 要低鹽低糖和少油
No stress, no loud noises, no physical exertion.
避免壓力、嘈雜聲和激烈運動
Just sit your ass down somewhere, man.
乖乖坐下來 兄弟
Tell him, Mike.
跟他說 麥克
And, honey, I'm doing it with you. We're now vegetarians.
老公 我們為了你全都吃素
Vegetarians? Look at me.
吃素?看看我
Look at all this man, baby. I'm brand new.
看看這個人 我重獲新生
I need animal sugars to survive.
我要吃肉跟糖才能活
Well, baby...
寶貝
I have a salad for you.
我替你做了沙拉
A salad?
沙拉?
Hey, T, looks like you got this under control. My tour of duty is done.
看來妳搞定他了 我的任務完成
Bye, Christine. Bye, Mike. Bye, guys.
掰 克莉絲汀和麥克 掰了
Hey, Mike. Wait up. Wait up, wait up.
麥克 等等 等一下
What you about to do? Can you run a quick-quick for me?
你要幹嘛?能不能幫我買東西?
Yeah, what you need?
好啊 你要買什麼?
I'll give you $1,000 for some Skittles.
我給你一千美元買彩虹糖
Marcus, I am not buying your ass no candy, man.
馬可斯 我才不要幫你買糖果
Okay, $2,000, Mike, for some Ding Dongs. And that's my final offer.
兩千美元 幫我買香腸 最後出價
I think you're gonna be Ding Dong-less...
你的小香腸會不見喔
like my soul.
就像我的靈魂
You always take whoever I love.
祢總是奪走我愛的人
This is Detective Mike Lowrey.
這是麥克勞里警探
The Captain is down.
隊長受傷倒地
He's my son.
他是我兒子
You got a fucked up family, Mike.
你的家人有夠變態 麥克
The Department of Justice has been investigating the corruption in the Miami Police Department.
司法部持續在調查邁阿密警局貪腐案
And we now have credible intelligence
我們掌握證據指出
that Captain Conrad Howard was directing these elements
康瑞德霍華隊長多年來
in coordination with the cartels.
直接和販毒集團合作
No, I'm not interested in approximately what time.
我對大概的時間沒興趣
I need to know exactly what time, do you understand?
我要知道確切時間 明白嗎?
You knew about this?
你早就知道了?
I found out two weeks ago.
我兩週前才知道
A press conference. Really?
公開記者會 真假?
I'm sorry about the way you had to find out.
很抱歉把你們蒙在鼓裡
But given your closeness-Our closeness?
但你們很親密 很親密?
Neither one of y'all would have a job if it wasn't for Captain Howard.
要不是霍華隊長 你們都不會有工作
Rita, you know this is not true.
莉塔 妳知道這不是真的
Honestly, I don't.
老實說 我不知道
The investigation has turned up new evidence.
這場調查挖出全新證據
Miami law enforcement's been a leaky ship for years now.
邁阿密警局多年來問題重重
Witnesses turn up dead, informants disappear.
證人莫名死亡、線人突然消失
Events appear random until you aggregate them over a period of years.
事件看似隨機 直到經過多年整合
Then a pattern emerges.
然後就出現了模式
Who is this?
那是誰?
Bud Grice, FBI, heading up the JTF on this show.
巴德葛萊斯 聯邦幹員 負責指揮這項聯合任務
That's who I am.
那就是我
Now, we knew someone was providing intelligence
我們知道有人提供情報
to a cartel moving product into South Florida.
給運毒到南佛州的販毒集團
We just didn't know who.
只是不知道是誰
A cartel banker turned up dead two weeks ago, shot by his girlfriend.
一名販毒集團銀行家兩週前被女友射殺
They found a phone with Howard's contact on it.
他的手機有霍華的聯絡方式
Years of communication with the cartel, account references offshore.
他多年來和毒販通訊 在海外開戶頭
Millions in Howard's name.
幾百萬美元都在霍華名下
Final piece we needed to nail that dirty motherfucker.
將這貪汙的王八蛋定罪的鐵證
Grice! Oh, whoa. Hey, hey, let me holler at you.
葛萊斯 讓我問你
You know I was with him when he went down, right?
你知道他中槍時我就在旁邊 對吧?
Call him dirty one more time.
再說一次他貪汙腐敗
I dare you.
我賭你不敢
We know he had others who were with him. We're gonna find them too.
他有同夥 我們也會揪出他們
I was with him.
我當時在他身邊
Put the cuffs on me right now. I was with him. Mike.
馬上銬住我 我跟他同夥
No, these motherfuckers think that just 'cause he's dead and can't defend hisself,
這群混蛋認為他死了不能為自己辯解
they gon' dump all this shit on him, burn his legacy.
就把錯全怪在他頭上 否定他的功勞
Not on my watch.
有我在就別肖想
This is Judy Howard, US Marshals.
這是茱蒂霍華 美國聯邦法警
I realise I have no jurisdiction here.
我知道我沒有管轄權
But as a professional courtesy,
但身為執法人員
I'd like to request visibility into the sources of the allegations against my father.
我想看到指控我父親的情報來源
Judy.
茱蒂
We're gonna figure this shit out, all right?
我們會查清楚的 好嗎?
How's Callie?
卡莉好嗎?
How do you think, Mike?
你覺得呢 麥克?
We're on the same team here, Judy.
我們是同一國的 茱蒂
Like hell we are, Mike.
才不是 麥克
My dad would still be alive if it weren't for your bastard son.
要不是你的私生子 我爸還會活著
Judy...
茱蒂
If I ever catch him out on the street, I swear on my father
他若被我逮到 我向我爸發誓
I will put him down.
我會殺了他
Come on. Come on, man. Come on.
我們走吧
So, what's our next move?
下一步是什麼?
They said he was working with the cartel. Let's ask the cartel.
他被指控和毒販合作 那就去問問他們
How you doin'?
你好嗎?
It's prison.
我在監獄
Yeah.
是啊
Look. We need your help.
聽好 我們需要你的幫助
They're saying that Captain Howard was dirty.
他們說霍華隊長貪汙腐敗
Do you know anything about that?
你知道這件事嗎?
How much time I get off for this one? I'm still working on that.
我能減刑多久?我還在爭取
This is me telling you that I need you.
我現在告訴你 我需要你
I need to know if Captain Howard was working with the cartels.
我要知道霍華隊長是否和販毒集團合作
No.
沒有
He was onto the ones that were.
他查到了內鬼
So he got greenlit.
所以才會被暗殺
Wait, no.
等等 不對
No, Captain Howard was killed because he was on your mother's hit list.
他是你母親下令暗殺的對象
He was added to it.
後來才加上他
Your people wanted it to look like us.
你們的人想嫁禍給我們
Your people wanted him dead.
你們的人想要他死
Whatchu mean, "our people"?
你說的“我們的人”是誰?
You should be careful.
你們應該小心點
You're playing a game and you don't even know the rules.
你們在玩一個遊戲卻不知規則
There's dirty players on your side. That's bullshit.
你們之中有內鬼 屁啦
Wait, who?
等等 是誰?
I saw him one time.
我看過他一次
Can you ID him? Si.
你能指認他嗎?
Give me a name.
給我名字
I don't know his name.
我不知道他的名字
My mother.
我母親
She's the one who dealt with him.
她直接跟他打交道
I knew we should have kept that damn witch alive.
我就知道應該讓那巫婆活著
Marcus.
馬可斯
May she rest in peace.
願她安息
Dude.
豬頭
Hey, boss.
嘿 老大
Our man on the inside got all of Howard's records in the JTF file.
我們的內線拿到霍華的記錄
Computers, phones, files, all of it.
電腦、手機、檔案 全都有
Well, we know Howard was onto our operation.
我們知道霍華查到這項行動
We just don't know how much he had. We need to make sure we got every trace.
但不知道他查到多少 我們得全都摧毀
That's beautiful.
非常好
Hey, boss.
嘿 老大
It's all the paper files. They're clean so far.
全都是紙本記錄 沒問題
Two phones had nothing. His office computer was empty.
他的兩支手機和電腦都刪光
He was careful. But?
他很小心 但是?
But his old personal laptop had weak encryption.
他舊筆電的密碼很弱
Here we go.
開始了
Shit. We tripped a fail-safe.
靠 我們觸發安全模式
The fuck you mean, "we"?
那是什麼意思?
Something was sent.
他傳送了什麼
To who?
傳送給誰?
Tracing the phone now.
馬上追蹤電話
What the hell?
搞什麼鬼?
He's texting us from the other side.
他從陰間傳簡訊給我們
No, he's not, Marcus.
才不是 馬可斯
If you're seeing this...
如果你看到這個
I'm probably dead.
我大概死了
Fuck!
靠!
Fuck me.
我靠
Before I begin...
我開始之前
I wanna say one thing:
我只說一件事
I'm putting you in mortal danger.
我讓你們有生命危險
Boys...
兩位
we got rats in our walls.
我們之中有內鬼
But I gotta make sure you're my bad boys.
但我得確定你們是我的絕地戰警
The Coke-bottle giant is the key.
那個可樂瓶巨人是關鍵
What?
什麼?
Don't trust anybody.
別相信任何人
What's that? What does that mean? "The Coke-bottle giant."
什麼意思?可樂瓶巨人?
Fletcher.
弗萊徹
Oh, shit.
慘了
These are the guys.
就是他們
We should put a bullet in these motherfuckers. Be done with it once and for all.
斃了這兩個混蛋就一了百了
Lintz, I love you. I'd like nothing more than to let you loose on them.
林茲 我也想讓你除掉他們
But extra dead cops doesn't do us any favours here.
但多死幾個警察對我們沒有幫助
Keep them under constant surveillance and see if they make a move.
全天候監視他們 看他們搞什麼
Fletcher's warehouse is right down that alley.
弗萊徹的倉庫就在小巷盡頭
Mike, I wasn't even gonna tell you this.
麥克 我本來不想告訴你
Then don't tell me.
那就別告訴我
No, you gotta hear this. This is big.
不 你得聽 這是大事
I can't die.
我死不了
What?
什麼?
Motherfucker, you did a pretty good job of dying at my wedding a couple weeks ago.
你兩週前在我婚禮上差點就死了
But I didn't.
但我沒死
Watch.
看好囉
Hey, Marcus.
嘿 馬可斯
Hey! Come on! Get out of the road!
嘿!
Hey! Marcus!
嘿!馬可斯!
Hey, stop, stop.
嘿 停車
What are you, some kind of moron?!
你是傻瓜嗎?
Stop, stop, stop.
別鬧了
Police! Stop!
警察!停車!
Hey! Bro!
嘿!
Slow down!
開慢點!
Crosswalk!
走斑馬線!
Talk to me.
說吧
You gotta trust, Mike.
你必須相信 麥克
Trust yourself. Trust the universe.
相信自己 相信宇宙
Stop that shit, Marcus.
別說那種屁話
It's not my time, Mike.
我的時辰未到 麥克
Oh, okay. So you're saying that if I shoot you in your face,
好吧 你是說我朝你的臉上開槍
you're saying that you won't die.
你也不會死
Fate dictates that you won't shoot me in the face.
命運決定你不會向我開槍
I'm saying... I'm... I'm saying that you saying
我是說你跟我說
that if I shoot you in your face, are you saying you won't die?
我向你臉上開槍 你說你不會死?
Fate doesn't deal in hypotheticals, Mike.
命運不管假設性問題
I'm gonna call the police.
我要報警喔
They're already here, ma'am. Mind your business.
我們就是警察 別管閒事
Just go to the beach.
去海灘玩吧
Stop that shit, Marcus.
別再鬧了 馬可斯
See? You're putting your gun away.
瞧 你把槍收起來
He's putting his gun away.
他把槍收起來
Ooh, Mike.
哇 麥克
Focus, man.
專心點
Yeah, I call this place, you know, Creative Space for Black Imagination.
我把這地方稱為黑人想像創意空間
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Thank you.
謝謝
What the hell is this place?
這是什麼鬼地方?
This is my studio gallery. I'm an artiste now.
這是我的藝廊 我現在是藝術家
Please, you ain't no damn artist.
拜託 你才不是
What do you guys want? Captain Howard.
你們想怎樣?霍華隊長
Yeah. I was sorry to hear what happened to him. He helped turn my life around.
真的很遺憾 他幫助我重獲新生
He told us to talk to you.
他叫我們來找你說話
Okay. Talk to me.
好吧 說吧
I just talked to you. Then say what you're supposed to say.
我剛剛說了 那就有話直說
I said what I'm supposed to say. You didn't.
我說了 並沒有
Then tell me what I'm supposed to say. I've said all I can say.
跟我說我該說什麼 我言盡於此
Fucking with us, beanstalk?!
你敢耍我們 樹人?
Marcus! Come on!
馬可斯 別這樣
Captain Howard saved my life. I'm not messing this up.
霍華隊長救我一命 我不能搞砸
I can't say what I supposed to say until you say what you supposed to say.
你說你該說的話 我才會說我該說的話
Dumbasses. Look.
蠢蛋 聽好了
Captain Howard was onto something big.
霍華隊長查到了大案
He didn't trust that you dumb fucks would figure it out, so he contacted me.
他不信你們兩個豬頭會懂 於是找上我
Because you're stupid, and I'm a genius.
因為你們是笨蛋 我是天才
So I protected the information in something.
所以我把情報藏了起來
In something beautiful.
藏進很美的東西
Flex your face one more time. Flex it again!
再嘟一下嘴試試看 快啊!
I will blow your fucking head off.
我會轟掉你的腦袋
Would you stop?! Come on.
別鬧了 拜託
In something that will live forever.
我藏在能永生的東西裡面
Did you shoot him?!
你向他開槍?
I don't think so.
應該沒有啊
Freeze!
別動!
Marcus. Marcus!
馬可斯!
You hit?
中槍了嗎?
Nah-ah.
沒啦
Black jellybean. Nobody likes that shit.
黑色雷根糖 誰都不愛吃
Whoa.
哇塞
Hey! Stop that stupid shit!
嘿!別做蠢事!
I'm not fucking with you! Stop!
我是說真的!別鬧了!
No! No, no! No! No!
不!不要!
I don't give a fuck!
老子豁出去了!
Marcus! No! No!
馬可斯!不!
What are you doing?!
你在幹嘛?
I got this! But you don't, though.
我行的! 你不行
No. No!
不!
Marc--!
馬可
Let's go! Let's move!
走吧!快啊!
Marcus!
馬可斯!
Burnett and Lowrey are moving north on 11th.
班奈特和勞里在11街向北走
Miami PD! Go!
邁阿密警察!快開車!
What are you doing?! I'm fightin' crime, baby!
你在幹嘛?打擊犯罪啊!
Freeze!
別動!
Mike!
麥克!
Have you ever had a panic attack before?
你有過恐慌症嗎?
What? Ain't nobody have no damn panic attack.
什麼?我才沒有恐慌症
You're at 165 over 90. Sweaty. Nauseous. There's no shame in getting counselling.
血壓飆升、全身冒汗 你該尋求諮商
All right. Thank you. Appreciate you, brother.
好啦 謝謝你 兄弟
Mike, let the man do his job.
麥克 讓他做好工作
Good job, man.
做得好
Hey, Mike.
嘿 麥克
What the hell you panicking about?
你在恐慌個什麼勁?
I'm not speaking to you.
我不跟你講話
What'd I do?
我做了什麼?
You two all right?
你們沒事吧?
Mike had a panic attack.
麥克恐慌症發作
He didn't. Mike is fine.
才沒有 麥克好得很
What happened?
發生什麼事?
Rita, you ain't gonna believe this shit. But we got a text--
莉塔 妳不會信 但我們收到
A tip. We got a tip that Fletcher had violated his parole.
我們收到線報弗萊徹違反假釋規定
So we came down here
所以才會來這裡
and obviously he was into some shit he ain't have no business.
他很顯然惹上不該惹的麻煩
Is that true, Marcus?
是這樣嗎 馬可斯?
Well, you know I was with Mike.
我都跟麥克在一起
How could you, of all people, think Captain Howard was dirty.
妳怎麼可以懷疑霍華隊長貪汙腐敗
I don't want this to be true.
我也不希望是真的
But it would benefit all of us to do our jobs and follow the evidence.
但我們都應該恪守職責調查線索
And you think he was stupid enough to put accounts in his own name.
妳真以為他會笨到用自己的戶頭?
He's being framed. By who?
他是被陷害的
That's what we're trying to find out.
我們也想查清楚
Rita, come on, you're smarter than this.
莉塔 妳沒這麼笨吧
Michael, please do not forget you're talking to your boss.
麥克 別忘了我是你上司
I'm trying to protect you here.
我這是在保護你
I got no footage for a two-block radius.
兩個街區內都沒監視影片
What?
什麼?
They must've killed all CCTV, all security cams.
他們一定切斷所有監視器
I got nothing.
什麼都沒查到
At least they ain't film your panic attack.
至少沒拍到你恐慌症發作
Hey, guys.
嘿 大夥兒
You had a panic attack? No.
你有恐慌症?沒啦
If you want, I can recommend a good counsellor. I'm good, Dorn. Thanks.
我能推薦好的心理師 不用了 多恩
Look, I shot this, went frame by frame.
這是我拍的 一格一格檢查
Check it out.
看看
All right. Not here.
別在這裡看
Dorn, shut it down. Yeah.
多恩 請大家離開 好
Hey. Let's go.
我們走吧
So, what is this?
這到底是什麼?
We're not exactly sure.
我們也不確定
Whoa. Wow.
哇 哇
There you go. There you go.
這就對了
All right, you fucks. Now that I know it's you...
你們這群廢柴 我知道會是你們
here it is:
我要說囉
I don't know how high up it goes, but there's corrupt officials on our side.
我不知道層級多高 但警局有內鬼
And they're working with the cartel.
他們和販毒集團合作
This all started smelling funny about nine years ago.
我九年前就覺得這件事有鬼
That shipment of coke we were about to raid went missing.
我們本來要沒收的毒品不見了
You know, I kept getting shut down from above.
我一直被上頭命令結案
So I pulled Sanchez and Ruiz outta retirement.
於是把退休的桑切斯和路易茲找來
I had 'em working on the outside, you know?
請他們私下調查 瞭嗎?
They were killed in a car crash a week later.
他們一週後就被車撞死
That shook me up.
我真的被嚇壞了
And it's why I never brought you two in.
所以才沒找你們倆
Well, shame on me for worrying about your asses when you coulda saved mine.
你們本來能救我 我不該擔心你們
But now it's up to you.
現在輪到你們了
Remember the bust back in 2003?
記得2003年的販毒案嗎?
314 pounds of ecstasy?
破獲了142公斤搖頭丸?
Well, I held onto the storage unit, off the books.
我私底下保留了那間倉庫
That's where the real files are.
真正的檔案在那裡
Everything you need to exterminate these rat fucks.
可以用來揪出那些內鬼
It's in there!
全都在那裡
You're gonna have to finish what I couldn't.
你們得完成我的任務
Please.
求求你們
Please, boys.
拜託了
You're my last hope.
你們是我最後的希望
2003.
2003年
That was the Haitians. Zoe Pound.
海地販毒集團佐龐
Where was their storage locker?
倉庫在哪裡?
I have no idea.
我不知道
All right. We need you guys to go down to the station and pull our original case files.
你們要回警局找到原來的案件檔案
That'll tell us where the locker is.
上面有倉庫的位置
Do it quietly and be careful. We don't know who we can trust.
千萬要小心謹慎 我們不知道能相信誰
Shit, this is heavy, man.
靠 這太沉重了
I'm just gonna come out with it. Clear the air.
先吐為快 避免尷尬
The rat is not me.
內鬼不是我
Thanks for that, Dorn.
多謝了 多恩
I feel safer.
我覺得更安全了
They just tried to kill my son.
他們想殺死我兒子
Because Armando can prove that Captain Howard was innocent.
艾曼多能證明霍華隊長是無辜的
Cap was onto these dirty players.
隊長查到那些內鬼
Armando told you that?
這是艾曼多說的?
Yes. It's the reason they wanted Captain Howard dead.
對 所以他們才殺死隊長
Armando can ID the guy that ordered the hit on Cap.
艾曼多能指認下令暗殺隊長的主謀
He have a name?
他知道名字嗎?
No. But a face.
不知道 但他認得他
Listen, I know y'all can do this. All right?
我知道你們辦得到 好嗎?
Just transfer Armando. Get him to Miami. Get him to a secure location.
把艾曼多轉移到邁阿密更安全的地點
We'll debrief him. We'll get his testimony. We'll get some pictures in front of him.
訊問他 拿到口供 給他看一些照片
But please do it now.
但請馬上行動
These guys are tryin' to cover their asses and they are not gonna stop.
這些傢伙想自保 不達到目的絕不罷手
Do it for Captain Howard.
為了霍華隊長
Look, the evidence against Captain Howard is overwhelming.
指控霍華隊長的鐵證如山
If I'm doing this, I'm doing it for you.
如果我這麼做也是為了你
All right, let's transfer Aretas.
好吧 讓我們進行轉移
You'll accompany him, get him to igloo here in Miami, do a debrief.
你要帶他來邁阿密訊問他
But I'm sticking my neck out and I'm trusting you.
但我是相信你才幫你忙
If he turns out to be bullshit, then it's gonna be my ass.
要是他瞎掰 我會丟掉工作
So don't screw me, Mike.
別搞砸了 麥克
Thank you.
謝謝你
Yeah?
喂?
We found Zoe Pound's storage unit.
我們找到佐龐的倉庫
We'll go get the files then take them to my houseboat for safekeeping.
我們會把檔案帶到我的船屋
All right, stay on it. Let me know when you got it.
幹得好 拿到檔案跟我說
Please surrender your firearms. They will be returned to you upon touchdown.
請交出手槍 降落後會還給你們
You good?
你還好吧?
Never been better.
好得很
It's about 45 minutes.
大概要飛45分鐘
Mike, I wasn't even gonna tell you this...
麥克 我本來不想說
but in one of our previous lifetimes together...
但在我們某個前世裡
you were a donkey.
你是一頭驢子
And I owned you.
而我是你的主人
You were a stubborn ass, Mike.
你是很拗的驢子 麥克
You used to bite and spit.
常常咬人和吐口水
You were nasty.
你超兇的
But I was a terrible owner, you know, because I used to beat you.
但我是個壞主人 我常常打你
Because you wouldn't listen for shit.
因為你不肯乖乖聽話
And maybe I beat some kind of shame into you, Mike.
也許你被我打到覺得超丟臉 麥克
And now I realise I was scarring your soul.
現在我知道我傷了你的靈魂
You miss your nap?
你沒睡飽嗎?
Mike, I'm trying to apologise to you.
麥克 我想向你道歉
We don't have your blankie, but you could just rest your eyes.
你沒有小被子 但可以閉目養神
That's exactly how you was as a donkey. Mm-kay.
你當驢子時嘴也那麼賤 好喔
That's that shit there. I get it.
你滿嘴垃圾話 我瞭啦
You need some help with your seat belt?
要我幫你繫安全帶嗎?
No, Donkey.
不用了 驢子
Hey. Bryant, this is Bronson.
布萊恩 我是布朗森
Other guys are on turnaround.
其他人在輪值
Take a seat.
坐吧
What's up?
怎麼了?
"US Marshal flight 724, we have an emergency.
“聯邦法警724班機發生緊急事故
Our prisoner has escaped custody with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
邁阿密警探勞里和班奈特幫助囚犯逃脫
There are officers down.
員警受傷倒地
Mayday, mayday. They are coming for the cockpit.
求救 他們要闖進駕駛艙
I repeat, they are hijacking the CH-47.
重複 他們想要劫機
All ground units please respond."
請地面單位回應”
Give me Lowrey's gun. Copy.
把勞里的槍給我 收到
Go, go!
快 快啊!
Get Lowrey.
搞定勞里
Let's go!
快點!
We welcome the storm, motherfu--!
風暴來襲 混帳!
Get me out of this fucking cage!
快放我出來!
Marcus!
馬可斯!
Mike!
麥克!
It's too heavy!
太重了
Don't let go!
別放手!
Grab the stick!
抓住桿子!
Where the hell you learn how to fly?!
你在哪裡學會開飛機?
I'm a drug dealer, man. To the right!
我是毒販啊 向右!
He was using my gun.
他用我的槍
How the hell did they get on a federal transport?
他們怎麼登上聯邦直升機?
We need to split up.
我們得分頭行動
We're gonna stay together.
我們要待在一起
Says who?
誰說的?
I'm not asking you.
這不是請求
I'm telling you. We're stayin' together.
這是命令 我們要待在一起
Fuck outta my way.
給我閃邊
Hey. Where--? Get the fuck off me.
你要去 別碰我
Hey! Hey!
嘿!嘿!
Look.
聽好了
You are the only person who can identify whoever is doing this!
只有你能夠指認這件事的主謀
The only way that any of us stays alive is if we get them before they get us.
我們必須先抓到他們才能活命
There's no us! There is no us!
沒有我們!沒有我們!
Damn.
該死
That Lowrey DNA is a bitch.
勞里的遺傳基因有夠強大
Y'all some strong motherfuckers.
你們都一樣固執
Okay. Now, look, everybody unflex. On three.
聽好了 你們要一起鬆手 數到三
One! Two!
一!二!
There you go.
這就對了
Captain Howard left us files that's gonna tell us who's doin' this.
霍華隊長留下來的檔案會透露幕後主使
Dorn has 'em.
多恩拿到檔案
We just have to get back to Miami.
我們只要回去邁阿密
You better not slow me down.
你最好別拖慢我
Lose your phones.
丟掉手機
You keep up with me or I leave you in the dirt.
跟不上來我就丟下你
You're in my world now.
你在我的地盤
Hey, Mike. Look, we gotta think about this.
麥克 我們得想清楚
I know you wanna move with him, you know, because he's your "son".
我知道你想陪著他 因為他是你兒子
Whoa, whoa. Don't air quote that.
喂 別做引號手勢
No, I didn't. I'm just sayin' I know why you tryin' to protect him.
沒有啦 我只是說我瞭你想保護他
'Cause he "family".
因為他是家人
Hey. Movin' the air quotes down to your hips doesn't un-air-quote them.
你在屁股後面偷做引號手勢也一樣
Just say he's my son.
說他是我兒子就行
He's your son. No, no.
他是你兒子 不對
Palms up is like you tryin' to say, oh, he's not really my son.
掌心向上代表你想說他不是我兒子
Oh. Well, your son's gettin' away.
是喔 你兒子逃走了
Shit.
可惡
If your men are on some kind of op, you might wanna pull us in.
妳的手下若在出任務 最好讓我們加入
Otherwise, it doesn't look good for them.
要不然他們情況不妙
Judy.
茱蒂
You ID the bodies? Roger. We got three unaccounted for.
確認身分嗎?有 三人失蹤
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas.
勞里、班奈特和艾瑞塔
Motherfuckers. Fucking--!
混帳東西 靠!
Shit.
該死
All right. Listen up!
好吧 聽好了!
We have three suspects, armed and dangerous, out there.
三名嫌犯持有武器 非常危險
And I want them back.
我要把他們抓回來
Let's go!
走吧!
Hold on. Judy.
等等 茱蒂
Three suspects?
三名嫌犯?
What do you think is happening here?
妳認為這是怎麼回事?
What do you think?
妳覺得呢?
Play the audio.
播放錄音
US Marshal flight 724, we have an emergency.
聯邦法警724班機發生緊急事故
Our prisoner has escaped custody with the aid of Miami PD Lowrey and Burnett.
邁阿密警探勞里和班奈特幫助囚犯逃脫
There are officers down. Mayday, mayday.
員警受傷倒地 求救
Come on, you can't possibly believe Mike and Marcus would do this.
拜託 麥克和馬可斯不會這麼做
Nah, you said it. Lowrey was obsessed with getting his son out of prison.
妳也說過 勞里一心想把兒子弄出監獄
Slow down, Judy.
慢點 茱蒂
This isn't Miami, Secada.
這不是邁阿密 塞隊長
These are my fugitives and right now the whole world is my jurisdiction.
他們是我的逃犯 不管在哪都歸我管
You've known them your whole life. How can you even suggest--?
妳從小就認識他們 怎麼能?
Do I think that Mike and Marcus planned this?
我認為這是他們的計畫?
Probably not.
大概不是
But people do things they wouldn't normally do when family's involved.
但人們會為了家人做傻事
In my experience innocent men don't run.
無辜的人不會逃跑
Can we stop and think before-Are you capable of doing your job?
能不能先想清 妳能恪盡職守嗎?
'Cause I need to move on.
我必須展開行動
They survived.
他們還活著
What the fuck you mean, they survived?
那是什麼意思?
No bodies on site. US Marshals are treating it as a manhunt.
沒找到屍體 聯邦法警展開追捕行動
These guys just refuse to die.
這些人就是不肯死
They're wanted men.
他們是通緝犯
Law enforcement and media are our friends now.
執法單位和媒體能幫我們
A manhunt for three fugitives
三名逃犯的追捕行動
is sending shock waves across South Florida.
震撼了南佛州
Ballistic reports have matched the bullets recovered from the bodies...
彈道報告符合嫌犯用的子彈
Are you planning on dropping out of the mayor's race in light of the recent events?
你打算因為最近發生的事退選嗎?
The manhunt is currently underway.
追捕行動已經展開
The FBI is assisting US Marshals in bringing these men in.
調查局協助聯邦法警追捕嫌犯
Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas should be considered armed and dangerous.
勞里、班奈特和艾瑞塔持有武器並且危險
These are individuals who have killed fellow law enforcement professionals.
他們殺害了同袍執法人員
If you see something, say something.
看到可疑人物 務必說出來
Put a bounty on the streets.
放出風聲懸賞他們
Get it to every gang in the city and let them fight for it.
讓每個幫派為了他們爭鬥
Five mil.
五百萬美金
Let's go get these motherfuckers.
我們去抓這些混球
The universe is crazy, ain't it?
這宇宙很瘋狂 對吧?
Look at us.
看看我們
I bet none of us thought when we woke up today this is where we'd be.
我們今天醒來都沒想到會落到這種下場
You outta jail.
你出獄了
We goin' to jail.
我們都會坐牢
This shit is special.
這件事很特別
Mike?
麥克?
Is there anything you would like to say to Armando?
你有話要跟艾曼多說嗎?
Fuck you talkin' to me like that? No.
去你的 我才不要
Mike, this is a moment. Express with your son.
這是最佳時機 跟你兒子談談
I'm sorry.
對不起
That's what I'm talking about.
我就是這個意思
For what? For everything, man.
為什麼?為了一切
Seems like bad shit happens to anybody I love, so...
我愛的人似乎都會發生壞事
Startin' to think maybe I'm cursed.
也許我受到詛咒
I just feel like...
我只覺得
maybe I cursed you.
也許我詛咒了你
You ain't fuckin' cursed me.
你才沒有詛咒我
Bad shit happens to everybody.
每個人都會發生壞事
Ain't always about you.
不一定都跟你有關
Hey, Armando.
嘿 艾曼多
I don't know if I told you this, but I died a couple of weeks ago.
不知道我有沒有說 但我兩週前掛掉
Sorry to hear about that.
真的很遺憾
Oh, no. The best thing that ever happened to me.
噢不 那是我遇過最棒的事
Shit's wild.
超誇張的
But y'all?
但是你們?
Y'all the reason I came back.
你們是我回來的原因
Hey.
嘿
Everybody, bring it in.
大夥兒 抱一下
Come on, bring it in. Come on.
來吧 抱一下 來吧
There you go, Armando.
這就對了 艾曼多
There you go. There you--
很好啊
Y'all are some terrible fuckin' fugitives.
你們是超遜的逃犯
What? Now, see?
什麼?瞧?
You makin' us look soft, like we don't know how to be on the run.
你害我們看起來像弱雞
Better get you out of this.
你最好換套衣服
Hey!
嘿!
That boy hard-headed. Chip off the old block.
那小子太衝動 有其父必有其子
Well, what we got here?
這是什麼情況?
Hey, Cain, come take a look at this!
肯恩 過來看看!
What are you boys doin'?
你們兩個小子在幹嘛?
"Boys"?
“小子”?
Are y'all stealing our clothes? Looks like it.
你們偷穿我們衣服?看來是喔
Fuckin' racism.
臭種族歧視
Y'all think just because we Black we stealin' your shit?
我們是黑人就會偷東西?
Now, these are my own Black clothes
這是我自己的黑人衣服
that I put on today from my own Black closet.
我今天從黑人衣櫥拿出來穿的
Marcus! What?
馬可斯! 幹嘛?
Look at your shirt.
看看你的帽T
How'd this get in my Black closet?
黑人衣櫥怎麼會有這件?
Why don't you boys sing us a little Reba song.
唱首天后瑞芭的歌給我們聽
Reba? Reba? Oh, yeah.
瑞芭的歌?好啊
Oh, please.
真是夠了
That's-'Cause he put... He put me on to Reb--
他要我唱瑞芭的歌
Which one? Which y'all--? Which one?
你們要我唱哪一首?
Sing your favourite.
你最愛的那首
Oh, she got plenty of them. 'Cause she got hits.
有很多耶 超多暢銷歌曲
Was it the up-tempo song? Or the slow jam? Yeah, yeah, remember the one?
快歌還是慢歌?記得那首嗎?
It was the slow one, nigga. Oh, okay.
那是慢歌 對吼
You hurt me in the morning Yes, 'cause she was hurt.
你今早傷害我 因為她很傷心
You hurt me at night Yes, yes.
你今晚傷害我 對啦
But I've changed Changed
但我改變了 改變了
And I'm strong I'm a woman
我很強壯 我是女人
I'm a strong Black wom--
我是強壯的黑人女
I'm a strong woman
我是強壯的女人
Yeah, 'cause she's not Black.
對啦 她不是黑人
And then...
然後
What you gonna do?
你要衝三小
That ain't no Reba song.
那不是瑞芭的歌
It's from her mixtape.
混音專輯有出過
Goddamn it!
該死!
We're sorry! We'll bring it back!
抱歉!我們會開回來!
We're not stealing your shit because we Black!
我們不是因為是黑人才偷東西
Did you ever love her?
你愛過她嗎?
What?
什麼?
My mother. You ever love her?
我母親 你愛過她嗎?
He's expressing.
他在跟你談心
I definitely loved her.
我當然愛她
And then you sold her out.
然後你出賣她
I made some mistakes.
我犯了一些錯
Like me.
像是我
You know that is not what I was trying-Now wait a damn minute, Armando.
我不是那意思 等等 艾曼多
He's trying to make up for it.
他想要彌補你
He don't owe you a damn thing.
他什麼都不欠你
All right, hold on. Hold on, Marcus. You're just... You're being aggressive.
冷靜點 馬可斯 你太兇了
I've been a dad a long time. He needs to hear this, Mike.
我當爸很久了 他得聽我說
He needs some tough-ass love.
他需要嚴厲的愛
Armando. Maybe he does owe you something. Okay?
艾曼多 也許他是欠你什麼
Your mom being deceived by him.
他欺騙了你媽
You being born in prison, in a web of lies
你在謊言中在監獄出生
that turned your ass into a stone-cold fuckin' killer.
所以才會變成冷酷無情的殺手
Yeah. You're a killer.
沒錯 你是個殺手
But this man, through it all, has been nothing but solid.
但儘管如此 這傢伙還是幫了你
That's some father-of-the-year shit right there.
你還真是年度最佳父親
Is it?
真假?
Your wack-ass parenting broke the truck.
你嚴厲的愛弄壞貨車了
My bad.
我的錯
Yeah, nah, that's dead.
引擎故障了
We're not far from Tabitha's.
泰碧莎就在附近
No, Mike. You know that woman's crazy.
不行 你知道她是肖婆
Yeah, but she likes me.
對 但她喜歡我
I don't think she likes you as much as you think.
她沒像你想的那麼喜歡你
The Pony's about two miles from here. What's The Pony?
小馬離這裡才三公里
I need my Instagram. I need my Friendster. I need more sex.
我需要IG、臉書和更多愛愛
I need more men in this club.
這裡要有更多男人
You all look beautiful. Now get back to work.
妳們都很辣 回去工作
Mike Lowrey. Damn.
麥克勞里 靠
What up, Tabitha?
怎樣 泰碧莎?
So y'all in trouble, huh?
你們又惹上麻煩?
Yeah, we need some help.
對啊 我們需要幫助
We need some clothes. No shit.
先換衣服 那還用說
A ride and some phones.
一輛車和幾支手機
Yeah. Guns too.
對 還要槍械
That's my son. That's Armando.
那我兒子 他叫艾曼多
You got you a little Spanish son?
你有個西裔兒子?
Yeah, it's a long story.
對啊 說來話長
Can you hook us up?
妳能幫忙嗎?
I mean, I got all that but what you gonna do for me?
當然囉 但你要替我做啥?
What you mean? We good for that.
什麼?妳能相信我們
You were.
那是以前
But you guys are men on the run now, so...
但你們淪為逃犯 所以
Well, what you need?
妳要什麼?
What I need?
我要什麼?
I need you to eat this pussy.
我要你幫我舔鮑
I'm not doin' that, all right?
才不要 好嗎?
Whoa, hold on, Mike, hold on. Think about this.
等等 麥克 考慮一下嘛
Now, you say guns and phones, right?
妳說槍械和手機 對吧?
Okay, well, look, you know Mike's a married man.
妳也知道麥克結婚了
So?
所以咧?
So he's gonna need some plausible deniability.
他要有合理否認的藉口
So I'mma have you lay down and stick out your tongue.
我要你躺平然後伸出舌頭
And you gonna have to do the rest.
其他的妳自己來
I can fuck with that.
我可以接受
Oh, yeah, go on, baby. No, Marcus.
來吧 寶貝 不 馬可斯
All you gotta do is close your eyes, Mike. No!
你只要閉上眼睛就行 不!
I'mma need pictures. You know how to take pictures, right?
我要照片 你會拍吧?
Hey. We don't have a lot of time. I need you to stop fuckin' around.
我們時間不多 別耍我
Oh, I'm not fuckin' around.
我才沒有耍你
All right, hey, let's go.
我受夠了 走吧
Wait, hold up.
等一下
Sit your motherfuckin' ass down.
給我乖乖坐下來
Hey, Tabitha, what is you doin'? What is you doin'?!
妳在幹嘛?你又在幹嘛?
Sit your married ass down! You get y'all asses down too!
給我坐下來!全都坐下來!
Shit. Everybody sit down.
可惡 大家都坐下來
Hey, I got the bad boys right here. Let's get that money.
我抓到他們了 把錢給我
Hey, Tab. Shut the fuck up.
嘿 小泰
Hold up, I'm confused.
等等 我被搞混了
You didn't want him to licky-licky?
妳不要他舔妳?
There's a $5 million bounty on your head.
有人出五百萬懸賞你們
I need that money. I was just stalling.
我要那筆錢 所以才拖延時間
That's... That's cold. He almost did that shit.
妳好壞喔 他差點就舔下去
He did not, Marcus.
並沒有 馬可斯
I told you she didn't like you.
我就說她不喜歡你
Get the fuck up.
給我起來
The bounty is dead or alive.
不管死活都行
Don't be stupid.
別做傻事
Hey, Armando.
嘿 艾曼多
If you live, I'll let you...
如果你沒死 我就讓你
What?
什麼?
I said if you live, motherfucker, holler at me.
你沒死的話再打給我
He was kinda cute.
他是小帥哥
We got a tip.
我們收到線報
Positive ID on our fugitives.
有人認出逃犯
Let's do this.
上吧
Mike, I'm about to make my move.
麥克 我要動手了
No, the fuck you're not. You about to go wherever these men are taking us.
不行啦 你要乖乖跟他們走
Oh, I'm not goin'.
才不要
Now I'll take the three in the front, you take the six in the back.
我解決前面三個 你處理後面六個
Marcus, we do not have any weapons.
馬可斯 我們沒有武器
In five... four... three...
倒數五、四、三
Ah, shit! This motherfucker.
慘了 這王八蛋
Fuckboy, fuckboy Whatcha gonna do?
幹男孩 你要衝三小
Ayo, Mike!
嘿 麥克!
Ain't no fun when the rabbit got the gun, huh?
只有我拿槍不好玩 對吧?
Wait, you know this guy?
等等 你認識這傢伙?
Yeah, I hit him with a hammer a couple years ago.
我幾年前用槌子K過他
You think I forgot about that fucking ho shit you pulled off at Manny's Prime Rib?
你以為我忘了你大鬧我的餐廳?
How the fuck did I let you two catch me?
我怎麼會讓你們抓到我?
Mike, I want my five million.
麥克 我要我的五百萬
Marcus!
馬可斯!
You see I got the fam with me. The streets!
我的兄弟都在 街頭霸王!
We could do this nice and easy or we can go to war!
你們不乖乖投降 我們就開戰!
'Cause I'm fucking war-ready!
我隨時都準備好!
What are you doing?!
你在幹嘛?
No!
不!
Go, go, go, go!
快走!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
倒車!
No! No!
不!
Windshield wiper fluid is flammable!
雨刷清潔液是易燃物!
How the hell am I supposed to know that?! I ain't no damn scientist!
我怎知?我又不是該死的科學家
Everybody relax. The fire's on the outside.
別緊張 只有車身著火
Oh, shit!
噢慘了!
Now it's on the inside!
車內也著火了!
Shit!
可惡!
Okay.
好吧
Everybody out! Everybody out!
快點跳車!
Shit.
該死
Open the damn door!
把門打開!
We can feel you right there, boy. Open the door.
我們知道你在裡面 開門
Hey!
嘿!
Open up, Muscle Milk.
讓開 肌肉男
Come on, man. What the fuck is you doing?
搞屁啊 你在幹嘛?
Nothing. It's just not a great time for me right now, guys.
沒幹嘛 但我現在不方便
It's not a great time for us either.
我們現在都不方便
Okay, let's reconvene in like an hour or so.
一小時後再碰面
Babe, we're out of body wash.
寶貝 沐浴乳用完了
What the hell?
搞什麼?
We found you guys.
找到你們了
We're in a relationship. Okay?
我們正在交往 好嗎?
Oh, okay. All right.
好吧
Sneaking around has been destroying me.
偷偷摸摸的很痛苦
It started about a couple months ago. It will not affect our professional lives.
兩個月前才開始 不會影響工作
Except for that one time in that van.
除了那次在廂型車
I am not sorry. Nothing to be sorry about.
我不後悔 沒什麼好後悔的
Yeah, you know. I mean, people do that shit.
對啊 大家都會做那件事
Are you guys okay? Yeah, we're good. I wanted to--
你們還好吧?很好啊 我想
What the fuck?! Okay. Whoa, whoa.
搞屁啊 別衝動
Hey, Kelly. Kelly.
嘿 凱莉
I asked you to wait outside for a second.
我請你在外面等一下
All right. Kelly, he's with us.
凱莉 他跟我們同一國
He can't be here.
他不能來這裡
This is my son, Armando.
他是我兒子 艾曼多
I know who he is, and that's why he can't be here.
我知道 所以他不能來這裡
I trust you with my life, Mike. But I as sure as shit don't trust him.
我信任你 麥克 但我不信任他
I trust him.
我信任他
Then take him to your house.
那就帶他去你家
Hey, Mike. Can I have a second with her, please?
麥克 讓我跟她談談
Yeah, yeah. Please.
好啊 沒問題
Hey, sweetie. Relax. Relax.
甜心 放輕鬆
Come here for a sec. Come over here for a second.
過來一下
We could both end up in jail.
我們都會坐牢
Give him a chance. Yeah, give him a chance to kill us all?
給他個機會 讓他殺死我們?
This is some dysfunctional shit.
這真是有夠混亂
She's fine. She don't look fine.
她沒事 看起來不像
I'm fine. Yes, you are.
我很好 是呀 身材的確很好
The fuck you say? All right, all right.
他說什麼?別激動
It's the language barrier. It was English.
有語言隔閡 他說英文耶
It was definitely English.
他絕對是說英文
Thanks for the drip.
多謝借我們衣服穿
Yeah. Okay, we're aggregating all the data.
沒問題 我在整合所有數據
There's over 100 hours of video, 200 units of audio.
一百多小時的影片、兩百多個音檔
We're indexing all audio, video and geo-located IP network data
我在整理所有音檔、影片和定位數據
to create a sight picture and develop a target package.
找到陷害隊長的那群壞蛋
Basically, you sifting through all this shit to find the guilty motherfucker.
你在篩選這一切 揪出壞蛋
Bingo.
答對了
Hey, Dorn.
嘿 多恩
Can you safely get me into my Ring app? I wanna see my family.
你能駭入監控器嗎?我想看看家人
Yeah, we got our own VPN and router. What's your username?
我有翻牆軟體 使用者名稱?
Marcus37.
Marcus37
Snickers89.
Snickers89
Almost home, baby.
我就快回家了
Hey, let's get to work. We got a lot to get through here.
事情很多 快幹活吧
So, what exactly are we looking for?
我們在找什麼?
We're looking for the guy who ordered the hit on Cap.
下令暗殺隊長的傢伙
Armando can ID him.
艾曼多能指認他
This fucking bastard has been my white whale.
這混球是我的終極目標
For the last nine years, I've been trying to harpoon the son of a bitch.
我這九年來一直想逮到這混帳東西
But now it's up to you.
但現在交給你們了
Ey-Ey-Ey. Do I walk into your house and show you how to make cocaine?
嘿 我有跑到你家教你製毒嗎?
Blow it up.
放大
It's him.
就是他
You sure?
你確定?
That's the guy that ordered the hit.
他下令暗殺行動
Bam. Got a name.
好耶 找到名字了
James McGrath. Army Ranger School, counterintelligence.
詹姆斯麥格拉 軍校畢業的反情報探員
Deployed in Mexico until 2005.
2005年前派駐到墨西哥
Worked with the DEA, Defence Attache's office.
曾為緝毒局和國防情報局工作
Oh, shit.
噢靠
He was taken hostage by your friends, the cartel.
他被販毒集團當成人質
He gave up his entire squad "under duress".
被逼供後招出整個小隊
It's called torture, man.
那叫做嚴刑拷打
He was the only survivor.
他是唯一倖存者
Cap had him the whole time.
隊長一直都手握證據
He just didn't know it.
只是不知道而已
Hello.
喂?
Hey. It's me.
嘿 是我
Damn it, Michael. Where are you?
該死 你人在哪?
Rita, we're coming in. We got proof that Captain Howard is innocent.
莉塔 證據顯示霍華隊長是無辜的
What proof?
什麼證據?
We got the guy that had Captain Howard killed.
我們找到下令殺死隊長的傢伙
Armando ID'd him.
艾曼多指認出他
Same dude that attacked us on the chopper. James McGrath.
就是在直升機上的詹姆斯麥格拉
Rita, we got ten years' worth of files.
我們有十年來的檔案
Cap was investigating these dudes. We got 'em all. It's a whole network.
隊長在調查他們 我們逮到他們了
We'll surrender to you tomorrow.
我們明天會去自首
Hey, look, we gotta go.
聽好 我們得走了
Michael, what--?
麥克 什麼?
You okay?
沒事吧?
They're coming in.
他們要自首
What?
什麼?
Michael says they have proof that exonerates Howard...
麥克說他們有證據能替霍華脫罪
explains everything.
解釋這一切
Do you still love him?
妳還愛他嗎?
What?
什麼?
No.
沒有
But I believe him.
但我相信他
Just be careful, babe.
小心點 寶貝
Still going to dinner?
還要一起吃飯?
Yeah.
對啊
They have the files.
他們拿到檔案
We need to make this look like cartel business. Spanish only.
我們要扮成販毒集團 只能說西語
Ammo's ready to go. Let's go.
彈藥備齊 走吧
We only need one hostage.
我們只需要一個人質
Shit! Shit! Shit!
可惡!
You guys! We got a problem.
大夥兒 有麻煩了
Miami Central, Miami Central. 29 in progress.
邁阿密警局 有人私闖民宅
Oh shit, that's my house.
靠 那是我家
Please advise, MOS residence.
請注意 那是警員住家
Respond forthwith.
立刻回應
Fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, no.
靠
Come on, Christine.
快接啊 克莉絲汀
Shit. Get a unit over to my house.
可惡 派小隊到我家
Come on, Reggie! Pick up! Pick up.
快接電話!
Miami Central, we have another 29 in progress.
發生另一起私闖民宅案
Please send units to Detective Lowrey's home address.
請派小隊前往勞里警探的住址
Enemy's down!
敵人倒地!
Reggie! You got incoming.
雷吉!
Get the family to somewhere safe. What?
帶大家到安全處 什麼?
Now! Yes, sir.
馬上! 是 先生
What's happening? What's going on?
怎麼回事?怎麼了?
There's people comin' in the house. I gotta keep y'all safe.
有人闖進來 我得保護妳們
Please be careful!
小心點!
Okay, Reggie, what's happening? Okay. Trust me. I love you.
相信我 我愛妳
Fuck! Fuck!
靠!
Behind you, Reg!
小心後面!
Oh, damn!
哇靠!
Who the fuck is this guy?! That's my boy! That's my boy!
這傢伙是誰?我的好女婿!
Damn!
太威了!
Come on, come on, come on.
快啊
No, no, no!
不 不!
Holy shit!
哇靠!
Come on, come on!
加油!
Chitty-Chitty-Bang-Bang, motherfuckers.
你們完蛋了 混帳東西
Me snacks is your snacks, Reggie.
我的零食就是你的零食 雷吉
All right, come on.
進去吧
Mike, did you see that shit?
麥克 你看到沒?
Pick up the phone.
快接電話
Whoa, Mike! Mike! Mike!
麥克!
One second.
等一下
Callie.
卡莉
I saw it on TV. My mom is after Uncle Mike.
我看到新聞 我媽在追捕麥克叔
There is no way that he did everything that they're saying.
他不可能做出那些壞事
Sweetheart.
寶貝
Everything is going to be okay.
一切都會沒事
Okay? Okay?
好嗎?
Hello? It's me. Get out of the house.
喂?是我 快逃出去
I've got Callie with me. Take her and go! Get out now!
卡莉也在 帶她走!快逃!
Callie, get behind me.
卡莉 躲在我後面
Mike.
麥克
Christine!
克莉絲汀!
Mr Lowrey.
勞里先生
Who am I speaking to?
你是哪位?
I think you know who you're speaking to.
我想你應該知道
I need your boy...
我要你把兒子
and whatever evidence your beloved captain had squirrelled away.
還有霍華隊長的證據全都處理掉
And for that, you can have your wife.
你只要辦到 就能救回你老婆
I'll call you back with instructions.
我會再打給你
Aw, shit.
噢慘了
Goddamn it.
該死
I'll go.
我會去
Let my life be worth something.
讓我死得值得
Never.
絕對不行
Mike.
麥克
He knew.
他知道了
What do you mean?
什麼意思?
He knew we were comin' in.
他知道我們要自首
He knew we had Captain Howard's files.
也知道我們有隊長的檔案
He knew we had ID'd him.
他知道我們認出他
How?
怎麼會?
Only person you spoke to was Rita.
我們只告訴莉塔
It's not Rita.
不是莉塔
Damn, she got bad taste in men.
靠腰 她超不會挑男友
Justice has been investigating the corruption in the Miami Police Department...
司法部正在調查邁阿密警局貪腐案
...with reports suggesting the late Captain Conrad Howard...
有關鍵報告指出
Hello?
喂?
...was directing these elements in coordination with the cartels.
霍華隊長和販毒集團合作
Allegations against Howard, which allude to include Lowrey and Burnett,
霍華的同夥包括勞里和班奈特
as well as giving up key witnesses, destruction of evidence,
並且供出關鍵證人、湮滅證據
and even the murder of fellow officers.
甚至殺害同僚警官
What's going on? I don't know.
怎麼回事?我不知道
There's been a breakthrough in the case. I need to get down to the station.
案情有突破 我得去警局
I'm gonna head down there.
我現在就去
I'm coming with you.
我要跟妳去
Who are you texting?
你在傳訊給誰?
Just... Just gotta get in touch with the office.
我得跟我的辦公室聯絡一下
JTF.
這是聯合專案
Gotta let everybody know.
必須讓大家知道
Hey. Honey. Come on.
親愛的 別這樣
Honey, what are you doing? Stop that.
妳在幹嘛?住手
What are you doing? Stop it.
拜託 別這樣
Let go of me. What are you doing?
放開我 妳在幹嘛?
Give it back to me. Give it back!
還給我 還來!
Fuck!
靠!
Hey, hey, come on.
嘿 來吧
You okay?
沒事吧?
Look at the phone.
看他的手機
You know you done fucked up, right?
你知道你完蛋了 對吧?
You all right?
妳沒事吧?
I'm sorry.
很抱歉
Ain't got nothing to be sorry for.
妳不必道歉
We'll find her, boss.
我們會找到她 老大
I don't trust anybody that's not standing right here, right now.
我只相信現在站在這裡的人
Every extra person that we involve
如果再有其他人參與
increases the likelihood that they know we're coming,
他們就有可能知道我們要來
which increases the likelihood that Christine and Callie
克莉絲汀和卡莉更有可能
don't make it out of there.
無法活著逃出來
That means no SWAT, no marshals, no backup.
不能派遣霹靂小組、聯邦法警或支援警力
It's just us.
只有我們
I never meant for it to go this way.
我不希望事情變成這樣
How did you mean it to go?
你希望變成怎樣?
After 9/11, nobody cared about drugs coming into this country.
911事件後 沒人在乎毒品問題
So to secure the borders we started to work with the cartels.
為了邊境安全 我們和販毒集團合作
And they kept us informed about any terrorist activity coming our way.
他們為我們提供恐怖活動的情報
And it worked. We haven't had an attack since.
很有效 後來就沒發生恐攻事件
We were protecting this country.
我們在保衛這國家
You were killing cops and getting rich putting drugs into this country.
你們殺害警察 又靠販毒獲取暴利
Rita. That's why you killed Howard.
莉塔 所以你才殺死霍華
He was onto you. You wanted to cover your tracks.
他盯上你 你想湮滅證據
No. That was McGrath.
不 都是麥格拉幹的
He's out of control.
他完全失控
Rita. Just take a second.
莉塔 想想看
I never meant for any of this to go this way.
我不是故意做出這一切
I guess I just need to know if it was ever real.
我只想知道我們之間是真的嗎?
It was always real.
當然是啊
I panicked. I lost control.
我慌了手腳 一時失控
Did you love me?
你愛過我嗎?
Yes.
當然
I swear.
我發誓
Well, that means...
那對我來說
We good. We got it.
搞定了
99% voice match.
99%聲音匹配
...absolutely nothing to me, you piece of shit.
毫無意義 你這個人渣
Hey. It's me.
嘿 是我
What the hell's going on?
到底是怎麼回事?
You screwed up is what's going on.
你搞砸了
We've been compromised. I'll explain when I get there.
我的身分暴露 我到了再解釋
We're moving the hostages. Cuba. Long-term hold...
把人質帶到古巴長期監禁
to keep Lowrey, Burnett and Aretas quiet while we sort this out.
讓勞里他們按兵不動 我們再想辦法
I'm bringing a seaplane. I'll be there at first light.
我會坐水上飛機在日出時抵達
All right, pack this place up.
把這地方收拾乾淨
All equipment and personnel prepare to move.
準備轉移所有裝備和人員
We're moving the hostages out of the country.
我們要把人質帶出國
What happened to your hand?
你的手怎麼了?
They call that a Colombian manicure.
這叫做哥倫比亞式美甲
What's so great about it
最棒的是
is it's the maximum amount of pain,
絕對會痛到極點
but you don't die.
但又不會死人
So now you've decided to be the one holding the pliers.
現在你決定折磨別人
Everybody breaks.
每個人都會招供
Everyone.
每個人
Your husband...
妳丈夫
is gonna kneel down in front of me...
會跪在我面前
and beg for your lives.
求我饒妳們一命
And then you're gonna watch me kill him.
然後妳會看到我殺死他
You don't know my husband.
你不了解我丈夫
Well, not officially, but...
我們沒正式見面 但
I look forward to seeing him again.
我很期待再見到他
Bad boys Bad boys
壞男孩 壞男孩
Come on, Mike.
唱啊 麥克
Whatchu you gonna do
你要衝三小
Yeah.
讚喔
What you gonna do When they come for you
他們來抓你 你要怎麼辦
That's enough, dawg. That's enough.
很好 好兄弟 夠了
Okay, well, we'll circle back on that one.
好吧 待會再繼續唱
All right. The plane is ready. We roll in 20.
飛機準備好了 20分鐘後出發
It's an abandoned amusement park. There should be no civilians.
那是廢棄遊樂園 應該沒老百姓
Plane is gonna land from the south. On the one side.
飛機要從南邊降落 第一組
Marcus and I will be on the plane.
我和馬可斯會在飛機上
Armando's gonna make his way in the water. The two side.
艾曼多要從水路過去 第二組
Kelly, Rita. This road is one way in, one way out.
凱莉和莉塔 進出都要走這條路
You're holding that road.
妳們要守住那條路
Dorn, you're gonna control the air.
多恩 你負責空中支援
Drones in the air, jamming is active, comms are secure.
無人機會干擾信號 通訊很安全
As far as they know, Lockwood is on his way with the plane
他們只知道洛克伍德坐著飛機
to move the hostages to Cuba.
把人質轉移到古巴
The second they get close to the plane with the hostages, it's quick kills.
他們帶著人質靠近飛機就格殺勿論
Neutralise all threats.
解除所有的威脅
These motherfuckers killed a lot of good cops.
這群混蛋殺了很多好警察
They have my wife, they have Callie.
他們抓走我老婆和卡莉
They attacked our families.
攻擊我們的家人
We not losing today.
我們今天不能輸
Hey.
嘿
We get on the ground, you even flinch,
降落後你敢亂來
you'll be dead in .24 seconds.
零點24秒內就會死
I concur.
我同意
I got one lookout on the platform outside.
戶外平台有守衛
I got one sniper on the roof of building two.
二號建築物屋頂有狙擊手
Tee those up.
給我看看
Everybody keep moving.
大家繼續行動
What are those? Gators.
那些是什麼?鱷魚
I thought it was an abandoned gator park.
我以為那是廢棄的鱷魚樂園
Abandoned by humans.
被人類丟棄
It's actually an old amusement park.
那是老舊的遊樂園
It sat on 10 acres, abandoned in 2017 after Hurricane Irma.
占地十英畝 2017年艾瑪颶風後遭廢棄
Their main attraction was an albino alligator named Duke...
最大的看點是一隻白鱷魚杜克
...who was 16 feet long, 900 pounds.
身長4.8米 體重408公斤
"And legend has it he's still there."
傳說牠還在那裡
Fuck that.
有夠靠北
Armando's at his QTH.
艾曼多抵達位置
Hostages are coming out now.
人質正走出來
McGrath plus three.
麥格拉和三名手下
Everybody stay calm.
保持冷靜
Mike.
麥克
Mike, do you have the shot?
麥克 能擊中目標嗎?
Negative. I do not have a shot. I do not have a shot.
不行 無法擊中目標
Mike, he's right there. I don't have it. I don't have it.
他就在那兒 我瞄不到
They stopped. Why'd they stop?
他們停下來 為什麼?
Shit.
慘了
Let's go.
走吧
Armando, they're closing in on you.
艾曼多 他們正走向你
Do they see him? I don't know.
他被看到了?不知道
Mike, now. Your chance is now.
麥克 現在是你的機會
They can see him. They know we're here.
他們看得到他 知道我們來了
I don't have it. Negative. Negative. Negative.
我瞄不準 射不中他
You gotta take the fuckin' shot.
你必須開槍
Armando's burnt.
艾曼多曝光了
Shit. Full green. Engage.
可惡
Kelly, get us there. Go, go, go!
凱莉 帶我們去 快點!
Contact, west dock side.
碼頭西邊有敵人
Dorn! Take out that sniper!
多恩!幹掉狙擊手!
Sending the drone.
派出無人機
Got him.
搞定他了
Not now, Mike!
別這樣 麥克!
Not now!
不是現在!
It's okay.
沒關係
Not your fault.
不是你的錯
Cut that bitch-ass shit out, Mike.
給我振作起來 麥克
I need Nasty Mike.
我需要狠角色麥克
Nasty Mike!
狠角色麥克!
Bad shit happens, but that doesn't mean you're bad.
壞事發生 但不代表你是壞人
Do that donkey shit, a'ight? That's what I'm talking about.
像一頭驢子 這才像話
That shit right there. That's that shit right there.
這就對了 你是狠角色
Bad boy. Bad boy. Bad Boy Mike. All right?
你是絕地戰警麥克 好嗎?
You're the big bad wolf in the neighbourhood
你是凶狠的大野狼
Not bad meaning bad but bad meaning good
你要使壞 但那是好事
Dorn, take out the vehicles on the four side. Copy.
處理掉那邊的車輛 收到
Go, go! Move it!
快上!
Sir! We're taking heavies. We lost the trucks and three guys outside.
對方砲火猛烈 失去貨車和三個人
Goddamn it!
該死!
Set firing positions, both sides. Let 'em in.
兩邊都派人把守 讓他們進來
Go.
快去
Marshal Howard, heat signature at the site of the AMMO van is showing explosions.
法警霍華 現場的熱能特徵顯示發生多起爆炸
ETA 15 minutes.
15分鐘後抵達
Dorn, we need cover and we need eyes inside. Go, now.
多恩 我們需要掩護和眼線 快點
Here comes the smoke.
我要發射煙霧彈
I got your six.
我會罩你們
Shoot those motherfuckers!
射下那些鬼東西!
Get those drones down now! Go!
快把無人機射下來!快啊!
Move, move, move!
快上!
Eyes up!
小心上方!
Oh, shit!
慘了!
It's like redneck Jurassic Park in here.
這就像臭白人開的侏羅紀公園
Let's get out of here, now.
我們快走吧
Kelly, go.
凱莉 快上
Dorn, back up Kelly inside. I'm going after Lockwood.
多恩 支援凱莉 我去追洛克伍德
Babe, I'm comin'.
寶貝 我來了
Armando, go for Callie!
艾曼多 去救卡莉!
Let go!
上吧!
Mike!
麥克!
Marcus!
馬可斯!
Go!
快走!
I'm out!
沒子彈了
Nice to meet you, Mr Lowrey.
幸會了 勞里先生
Grenade!
手榴彈!
Oh sh--!
噢慘了
Holy shit!
哇靠!
Hang on!
坐好!
Stop!
住手!
Christine!
克莉絲汀!
Shit.
可惡
Oh sh--!
慘了
Mike, I got this! No. No, no!
我來救你 不要!
Here I come, baby! Here I come!
我來了 寶貝!
No! No! No!
不!不要!
Marcus!
馬可斯!
What? Behind you.
幹嘛?你後面
Oh, shit.
慘了
I got this, Mike.
我行的 麥克
It's just Dukey, baby.
只是杜克而已
Marcus, my gun. I dropped my gun in the water. It's by your foot.
我的槍掉進水裡 就在你腳邊
I don't need no gun, Mike.
我不需要槍
Begone, gator.
退下 鱷魚
This is not your place, Duke.
這裡不屬於你 杜克
I rebuke you!
我命令你!
See, Mike?
看到沒?
That's how you command the universe.
這就是控制宇宙的方法
Where's the gun? Where's the gun? Oh, shit!
我的槍呢?靠!
Go, go.
快走
That motherfucker racist, Mike. That motherfucker racist!
那隻白鱷魚歧視黑人!
Mike sent me.
麥克派我來
I need you to trust me.
妳要相信我
Run.
快逃
Run!
快逃!
Come on. Come on. Get up.
振作點 起來
Stop!
站住!
Go! I'll slow you down.
去吧 我會拖慢你
Eyes on location.
看到目標了
Oh, shit.
有夠慘
You alive?
你還活著?
Shit.
天啊
Okay. Hey.
沒事了
Rita, stop this. You don't want to shoot me.
莉塔 住手 妳不會開槍的
You're right.
你說的對
Come here. Okay. Okay. It's okay.
來吧 沒事了
I fuckin' hate politicians.
我超討厭政客
Let's move! Go, go!
上吧! 快上!
Fan out. Take the team upstairs.
分頭行動 帶小組上樓
No targets.
目標不在這裡
Go topside!
到屋頂!
Okay. Okay, here.
在這裡休息
Put me down. It's okay. Okay.
放我下來 沒關係
You okay? Yeah. Yeah.
你沒事?沒事
Thank you.
謝謝你
I've been here before.
我來過這裡
Oh, shit.
噢慘了
How did you let him catch you?
你怎麼會被他逮到?
He's sneaky as hell, Mike.
他超狡猾的
Your wife and I were having a debate.
你老婆跟我爭論
She seems to have an inflated impression of you.
她似乎高估了你
Mike. Hey, bae.
麥克
Nevertheless, this is the end of the road.
不管怎樣 就快結束了
One of them is about to die.
其中一個必須死
You choose.
你來選擇
What you don't know, Mr McGrath...
麥格拉先生 你並不知道
is one of 'em can't die.
其中一個死不了
Who you talking 'bout?
你說的是誰?
A wise man told me I was gonna have to make a hard choice.
有位智者說我必須做出艱難抉擇
You need to check with that motherfucker before you out here choosing shit.
你在亂選之前最好問問那混蛋
You have five seconds, Mr Lowrey.
你只有五秒 勞里先生
We gonna need some more time, sir.
我們需要更多時間
Four... three...
四、三
Mike. Don't you do no dumb shit.
麥克 別幹傻事
...two...
二
Mike. Mike. Hey. Hey. I'm here.
麥克 我在這裡
Motherfucker done shot me.
臭王八蛋開槍射我
Aw, damn.
有夠痛的
Here. Let me check it. Let me see. No, Mike. Your donkey ass shot me again.
讓我看看 不要 你這驢子又射傷我
Let me look at it. Don't touch me with your donkey hooves, Mike.
讓我看看 別用你的驢蹄碰我
Damn, man.
有夠夭壽
Listen. I had to fucking take the shot.
聽好 我必須開槍
No, Mike. No.
才怪
Marcus. Let me take a look.
馬可斯 讓我看看
You see that shit, Christine?
看到沒 克莉絲汀?
I shot you in your vest. Stop bitchin'. It don't matter. Okay?
我射中防彈背心 別碎唸 不重要啦
You see what you done devoted your life to, Christine?
看到妳的終身伴侶嗎?
I've got eyes on Aretas. Moving in.
我看到艾瑞塔 接近中
Shit. That's Judy.
靠 那是茱蒂
Armando, do you copy?
艾曼多 收到嗎?
Oh, shit.
慘了
Mom. Mom, don't.
媽
Get away from her.
離她遠一點
Mom. Now!
媽 馬上!
Mom, listen to me, you don't understand.
聽我說 妳不懂
Callie, I need you to listen to me.
卡莉 妳得聽我說
I want you to step slowly to your right and walk towards me.
我要妳慢慢從右邊走向我
Mom. Mom, I'm fine, okay?
媽 我沒事
Callie, I need you to move out of the way.
卡莉 我要妳讓開
Mom.
媽
Mom, don't shoot, don't shoot! Mom, he saved me. Stop!
媽 別開槍!他救了我 住手!
Judy! Judy!
茱蒂!
Back off, Mike! Put the gun down.
退後!把槍放下!
He saved my life.
他救了我
Please, Mom.
拜託 媽
Mom. Mom.
媽
Are you hit? Are you hit?
你中槍了嗎?
I'm good.
我沒事
You good?
你沒事?
You did good. You did good.
你做得好 做得好
Howard. Where are you?
霍華 妳在哪裡?
Howard. Do you copy?
霍華 收到嗎?
Go.
走吧
Before I change my mind.
免得我改變主意
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
我們走吧
Hey. You good? You good?
嘿 沒事吧?
Hey.
嘿
Take this.
拿去
Head south. Don't look back.
往南走 別回頭
Hey.
嘿
Be good.
要當個好人
It's not up to you, detective.
你管不了我 警探
Come on, come on. We got injured cops here.
快點 有警察受傷
I need you to bring the writ to me now.
馬上把傳票拿給我
I know, I know, I know.
我知道很痛
How is he? You know, he'll pull through.
他怎樣?他會撐過去
Don't kiss him, Christine.
別親他 克莉絲汀
Mike, in our next life, you coming back as a pair of my shoes.
麥克 你下輩子會是我的鞋子
And I ain't gonna wear no socks.
我不會穿襪子
And I'mma step in all kind of shit.
而且會踩各種髒東西
Miami DA and mayoral candidate Adam Lockwood and former Army Ranger James McGrath
邁阿密市長候選人亞當洛克伍德
were killed this morning in a firefight.
今早在槍戰中喪命
It is believed that Lockwood and McGrath were the key links
他們是邁阿密執法單位
between Miami law enforcement and cartels.
和販毒集團的同夥
The late Captain Howard has been fully exonerated.
已故霍華隊長完全洗清冤屈
Co-conspirators are currently being rounded up by the FBI and the Miami PD.
調查局和邁阿密警局正在逮捕其餘共犯
The search for convicted killer Armando Aretas continues.
艾曼多艾瑞塔的追捕行動持續進行
The fugitive remains at large.
這名逃犯仍然逍遙法外
Hey, hey, hey. My people.
嘿 大家好
Where's Theresa? She's with Little Marcus by the swings.
泰瑞莎呢?她在陪小馬可斯盪鞦韆
Hey. I'm about you hook you all up.
我要烤肉給你們吃 我們餓扁了
Watch this.
看我的
Partner.
最佳拍檔
What's all this?
你在搞什麼?
Why you got on an apron?
幹嘛穿上圍裙?
Work on my grill skills.
我要來燒烤啊
No, Mike, you gotta earn the grill.
不行 你得先學會燒烤
This takes seasonings and temperatures. You can't just be cooking on my grill.
靠的是調味和溫度 你不能用我的烤架
Your grill? Joker, this is a public park.
你的烤架?這是公園耶
You don't own every grill you see.
這些烤架不是你的
You know what, Mike? Why don't you go make some potato salad and set the table.
這樣吧 你去做馬鈴薯沙拉和擺桌子
Oh, you talking dirty.
你這是在侮辱我
Now, look. I don't... I don't know what you got going on
我不知道你憑什麼覺得
with your barbecue dictatorship in your mind, but I ain't the one.
你才是燒烤大師 但我不鳥你
I'm cooking on this grill whether you like it or not.
我要用這個烤架 你管不了我
Hey, Mike-Excuse me, sirs.
麥克 請讓開 兩位先生
What are you... What you doin', Reggie?
你在幹嘛 雷吉?
Request permission to cook my chicken.
請允許我用烤架烤雞
Permission denied, Reggie. Go ahead somewhere, man.
我不允許 去別的地方
Take your smock off and go play with the kids.
脫掉圍裙去跟小朋友玩
Listen, this is the man area of the barbecue.
這是正港男子漢的烤架
Look, you know what? All due respect, we appreciate that you did save people that we love.
老實說 我們很感謝你救了我們的家人
We appreciate that, right? Yeah, we appreciate that.
感激不盡 我們衷心感激你 雷吉
Now, back the fuck up. Yeah.
現在給我滾 沒錯
All right, look. I'm willing to compromise with you.
我願意為你退讓一步
You can work that half of the grill. It's small. And I'll work this half.
你用那一半 我用這一半
Is he still standing there?
他還站在後面?
Yes, he is.
是的
Huh, that's weird.
好奇怪
He think he hard now.
他自以為是硬漢
You need to let that motherfucker know he ain't cooking no chicken out here today.
你得讓他知道他今天別肖想要烤雞
Mike. He killed 15 people at the house.
麥克 他一口氣幹掉15個人
So, you not gonna handle this shit.
你不會搞定他囉
Yeah, I'm gonna let that motherfucker cook the chicken.
對啊 我會讓他烤雞
Yeah, there's something weird in his eyes. So I'mma make the potato salad.
他的眼神怪怪的 我去做沙拉
I'mma set the table. Yeah.
我去擺桌子 好
Permission granted, Reggie. There you go.
你得到允許 雷吉 來吧
Come on. Bring your ass on.
快點 別拖拉了
It's too hot out here for this shit.
熱得要命 沒空奉陪
Wish I had a horse. At least I could ride that motherfucker.
真希望我有馬 起碼可以用來騎
I curse you, donkey.
我詛咒你 驢子
I curse you for all lifetimes.
我詛咒你生生世世
You mother--
去你媽的
Fuck you, Marcus.
去你的 馬可斯